### Contact

brittanyelaine.white@gmail.

www.linkedin.com/in/brittanypickney-bsn-rn-cmsrn (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Healthcare
Microsoft Office
Healthcare Management

### Certifications

Certified Medical Surgical Nurse Chemotherapy/Biotherapy Certified

# Brittany Pickney MSN RN CMSRN

Bone Marrow Transplant RN at Texas Children's Hospital Houston, Texas Area

## Summary

Experienced certified Medical-Surgical RN with a strong history of working in surgical oncology. Currently working with Bone Marrow Transplant population in an Infusion center with various, cutting edge chemotherapies, biotherapies and CAR Tcell infusions. All of work experience in a variety of large academic/teaching hospitals. Motivated and energetic leader in pursuant of MSN in Nursing Administration and Leadership from the University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston. Special interest in patient safety, nursing education, wound care and patient-centered rounding. Current roles include: Infusion Charge RN, Central Line Nurse Champion, Skin Resource Nurse/Champion, Unit Quality Practice Council, Chemotherapy Administration Certified.

## Experience

Texas Children's Hospital RN November 2017 - Present (2 years 8 months)

MD Anderson Cancer Center Registered Nurse Coordinator November 2015 - November 2017 (2 years 1 month)

CHI St. Luke's Health - Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center Registered Nurse August 2011 - November 2015 (4 years 4 months)

### Education

Houston Baptist University BSN, Nursing · (2006 - 2011)

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Master's degree, Nursing Administration · (2016 - 2019)